dealiciousmom.com 2019-07-18

# About Dealicious Mom

Hi, my name is Sara. I am the Founder of “Deal”icious Mom. I’m a wife, mom to two amazing boys and a brand new baby!! I also work as a special education teacher and am not sure I have room for anything else but I sure can try! So as you can see my days are pretty full… but not full enough for me not to be addicted to deal hunting as well! I am on the constant search to get things for free or close to free. I founded Dealicious Mom in 2008 to share my deals and steals with you. So if you enjoy our blog or you would like to help in our quest, please leave a comment, sign up for our feed or email subscription and share in the fun!

Our community of moms has grown over the years and become a destination that helps us all live the sweet life AND spend less. Please don’t hesitate to reach out to me and our panel of moms. We look forward to connecting with you!

CONTACT US:

To reach Sara, Lisa or any of our local mom bloggers around the country please send an email to DealiciousMom (at) Gmail (dot) com

Follow us on Twitter [here](http://twitter.com/DealiciousMom)

Be our friend on Facebook [here](https://www.facebook.com/DealiciousMom/)

Get our daily email of all my deals, freebies and tips [here](https://www.dealiciousmom.com/connect) – this is the best way to stay up to the minute on deals, freebies, and tips without having to check this blog throughout the day.

As seen on The Talk, Kurt the Cyber Guy, and in All You Magazine

For questions about our shop and items purchased directly through “Deal”icious Mom (i.e. returns policy) please visit our [FAQ](http://www.dealiciousmom.com/faq/)

> Here’s my **disclosure policy** : To get your own policy, go to http://www.disclosurepolicy.org This blog does not contain any content which might present a conflict of interest. The owner(s) of this blog is compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics. Even though the owner(s) of this blog receives compensation for our posts or advertisements, we always give our honest opinions, findings, beliefs, or experiences on those topics or products. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely the bloggers’ own. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question.

> This blog is a personal blog written and edited by Lisa Waddington with input from our national panel of mom bloggers. This blog accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions or other forms of compensation. This blog abides by word of mouth marketing standards. We believe in honesty of relationship, opinion and identity. The compensation received may influence the advertising content, topics or posts made in this blog. That content, advertising space or post will be clearly identified as paid or sponsored content.    

Here’s my **Privacy Policy**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit  
our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these then[ click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy..

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

• To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

• To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect information when users visit our site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on our site, other websites and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, check out [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

This policy was last modified on June 29, 2010

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

http://www.DealiciousMom.com

PO Box 2502, Winter Park, FL 32790, USA
